muih.edu 2017-12-13

# Privacy Policy | MUIH

Maryland University of Integrative Health considers the security and maintenance of Confidential Information a matter of high priority. The MUIH community is committed to honoring the relationships it has one to another and upholding the expectations of confidentiality within those relationships. We are committed to complying with laws governing Confidential Information, including the federal Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, requiring financial institutions (including educational institutions) to ensure the security and confidentiality of customer records and information; the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) governing Protected Health Information; and the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), governing Educational Records. And we respect the need to maintain as Confidential Information corporate information.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell, share, trade, or give away your name, purchase, or donor history to other organizations without your specific consent. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping web experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

#### What information do we collect? How do we use it?

We collect the domain name of email addresses of visitors to our site and aggregate (not personally identifiable) information on what pages visitors access. We use this information to monitor the use of the site and to improve its performance and usefulness. We also collect information you volunteer, such as survey responses, comments, purchasing and billing information, and your requests.

When you make a payment, we need to know your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number, CVC code (on the back of your card) and expiration date. This allows us to process your payment, fulfill your registration or order, and notify you of your status. We do not keep credit card information on file once payments have been processed.

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. See information about our Email Communication below.

We do not share your information with outside companies.  We may release your information when required by federal, state, or local regulations.

#### How do we protect customer information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

#### How do we allow customers to update or change the information we collect?

You may update or change information related to your account by updating your profile, accessible via the home page once you are logged in, or by sending us email. Yes, we do use cookies, but we do not overuse them! We use cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience. The text in a cookie, by itself, only tells us that you have visited our site before. It does not store any personal information such as your name, email address, street address, or phone number. Cookies are also used to maintain your shopping basket. All data contained in the shopping basked is kept on our server and not in the cookie your machine is assigned.

#### Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information. If we find it necessary to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please also refer to the Terms of Use regarding use of the University’s website.

#### Tell Us What You Think

We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. If you have any questions, please [email us](mailto:webmaster@muih.edu), call us at 410-888-9048, or write us: Maryland University of Integrative Health, 7750 Montpelier Road, Laurel, MD, 20723.

#### Email Communication

If you choose to be included on our email list, we may monitor and make use of your user activity, such as the website address or specific link from which you accessed our website. We track correspondence in order to provide you with more relevant information, including regarding academic programs, admissions and alumni announcements, or other University news. You may choose to opt out of email communication from us at any time. Please email [webmaster@muih.edu](mailto:webmaster@muih.edu) to unsubscribe. At the time of sending any email communication to you, we will also give you the opportunity to unsubscribe from our email list.

#### Guidelines Regarding Do Not Mail and Do Not Call

When it comes to keeping you informed, our Marketing Department may contact you in one of three ways: direct mail, telemarketing or email. If you prefer not to be contacted by one or more of these methods, or if you prefer not to be contacted at all, please [email us](mailto:webmaster@muih.edu), call us at 410-888-9048, or write us: Maryland University of Integrative Health, 7750 Montpelier Road, Laurel, MD, 20723. Whatever your preference we will honor it for a period of three years.
